There are two sides to every lie.
The Imposter is a documentary, mystery, crime film directed by Bart Layton.
In 1994 a 13-year-old boy disappeared without a trace
from his home in San Antonio, Texas.
Three-and-a-half years later he is found alive thousands of miles away in a village
in southern Spain with a horrifying story of kidnap and torture.
His family is overjoyed to bring him home.
But all is not quite as it seems.
Self, played by Frédéric Bourdin.
Frédéric Bourdin, played by Adam O'Brian.
Carey Gibson, played by Anna Ruben.
Nancy Fisher, played by Cathy Dresbach.
Charlie Parker, played by Alan Teichman.
Social Worker, played by Iván Villanueva.
The Imposter is a 2012 documentary film about the 1997 case of a French confidence trickster Frédéric Bourdin, who
pretended to be Nicholas Patrick Barclay, an American boy who had disappeared in Texas at the age of 13 in 1994.
The film was directed by Bart Layton.
It mainly includes interviews with Bourdin but also with members of Barclay's family, as
well as archive television news footage and reenacted dramatic sequences.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, investigation,
fake identity, biography, disappearance.
The tone is mind_bending.